<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252" ?>

<string_table>

	<string id="esc_viktor_name">
		<text>Viktor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_cherry_name">
		<text>Cherry</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dima_name">
		<text>Dima</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_atreo_name">
		<text>Atreo</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_vovan_name">
		<text>Vovan</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_leto_sub_name">
		<text>Leto</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_stalker_generic_name">
		<text>Stalker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pda_generic_name">
		<text>PDA recording</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_monolito_generic_name">
		<text>Monolith Soldier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_deber_generic_name">
		<text>Duty Soldier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_generic_name">
		<text>????</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_bandido_name">
		<text>Bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_bandidos_name">
		<text>Bandits</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_trodnik_name">
		<text>Trodnik</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_trodnik_pda_name">
		<text>Trodnik's PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_radio_name">
		<text>Radio</text>
	</string>
	<string id="viktor_dialog_reject_way_0">
		<text>I shouldn't go there...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="viktor_dialog_reject_lab_way_0">
		<text>I can't go back now. I have to end this once and for all.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_hi_msg">
		<text>You’re finally awake, stalker. Come on, let’s talk for a bit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_0_msg">
		<text>Looks like it fits you well. I thought it might be too big for you... Alright then, follow me and don’t stray too far.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_salida_0_msg">
		<text>Alright. I’ll follow you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_encandila_0_msg">
		<text>Hope the light didn’t blind you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_1_msg">
		<text>Look, my friend. Come closer. From here you can see them resting: a pack of fleshes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_salida_1_msg">
		<text>...Fleshes? What are those?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_2_msg">
		<text>Get ready, Viktor. Hold the grip tight or it’ll snap your wrist. If you need to reload, pull the latch back from the barrel and load in a few shells.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_salida_2_msg">
		<text>But what the hell are fleshes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_viktor_msg_1">
		<text>What the hell were those things? Were they pigs? They were all deformed!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_2b_msg">
		<text>Yeah, and that’s not the only ugly thing you’ll see around here. The place is crawling with nasty bandits too... If you’ve got the stomach for it, you can go up with your knife and carve out their eyes or some meat. sometimes stalkers buy that stuff. I’m going to check the area—don’t you dare lower your guard.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_3_msg">
		<text>Listen, I found a trail and it’s definitely not from the fleshes we just killed. Follow me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_4_msg">
		<text>They’ve set up a camp, and I think I know who it was...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_salida_4_msg">
		<text>Who? More fleshes?!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_4a_msg">
		<text>No. those things don’t pitch tents. (laughs)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_5_msg">
		<text>I knew it. That campfire was used recently. Viktor, get ready. The bandits are up to something—we’re going to pay them a visit.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_salida_5_msg">
		<text>Bandits!? I didn’t realize we were dealing with people. What the hell do we do?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_5b_msg">
		<text>Let me go in first. Stay put and wait for one of them to show up—then take the shot. After that, whatever we find is yours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_salida_5b_msg">
		<text>Alright. I’ve got you covered. I’ll stay right behind you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_viktor_msg_2">
		<text>My wrist hurts... and my hands are shaking. I’ve never killed anyone before.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_salida_6_msg">
		<text>The shaking will pass in a few minutes... it happens to all of us. If it helps, they would’ve done far worse to you if they’d had the chance, bandits show no mercy. Anyway, let’s talk for a moment. I found something interesting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_nimble_1_msg">
		<text>Hey! You’re Viktor, right? Welcome to the Zone. Viper gave me your contact. Meet me at the house west of the Rookie Village.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_nimble_2_msg">
		<text>Watch out for bandits.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_nimble_3_msg">
		<text>Viktor! I managed to get the box open. Swing by and we’ll talk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_trader_msg_1">
		<text>Viktor, I’ve got some information that might be really useful to you. Stop by and we’ll talk it over.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_trader_msg_2">
		<text>You must be the new guy. Vinicio, right? Make yourself comfortable. Let’s have a good chat.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_trader_msg_viktor">
		<text>The name's Viktor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_trader_msg_3">
		<text>Yeah, whatever. Viktor, come in.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_0">
		<text>Go on, don’t worry about it. There’s a bit of an irregularity in the readings among those crates and bits of scrap metal. Just stand right there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_viktor_msg_0">
		<text>Right here, correct?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_1">
		<text>Excellent! Right where I said it would be. Despite the radiation, you’re handling it remarkably well.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_viktor_msg_1">
		<text>Yes, yes. Where do I go now!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_2">
		<text>See the remains of that crane cabin up ahead? Yes, right there. That’s the spot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_3">
		<text>Good. No time to poke around in stashes—just ignore everything or the radiation’s going to leave you bald.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_viktor_msg_3">
		<text>Hurry up! Where the hell am I supposed to go now!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_4">
		<text>Head for the outlet of that concrete-covered steel pipe. Check around there, alright? Hurry up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_5">
		<text>Hmm... the radiation levels are a bit higher than normal. You’d better run. The next spot is right behind you—near that old, rusted truck cargo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_viktor_msg_5">
		<text>So... Where now!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_6">
		<text>Oh, I thought I’d already said it. On the ground, circle around the tree to your right and head over there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_7">
		<text>Alright, I’ll mark the next one on your PDA. It’s a bit tricky to explain. You’ll need to get close to the anomalies... so be careful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_8">
		<text>Ok, there's just 10 remaining spots.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_viktor_msg_8">
		<text>10!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pollo_task_msg_9">
		<text>Just kidding, bro. Get out of there already. Come over and I’ll give you some medkits and a well-deserved reward.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_mago">
		<text>Hey, look. There goes the one who killed the Mage.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_fanatico">
		<text>There goes the guy who beat you to that fanatic job. Heard he’s quick.”</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_tejado">
		<text>Psst, look. That’s the stalker who’s been climbing rooftops.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_controlador">
		<text>Hey! Thanks for dealing with the mutant in the tunnel. I’d been meaning to head to the swamps for a while now...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_aldea">
		<text>There goes Viktor. Thanks for keeping the village safe, brother.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_salvado">
		<text>Isn’t that the one who saved you the other day?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_hook">
		<text>Isn’t that the guy Hook’s been looking for?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_arrastrado">
		<text>That’s the guy Viper was dragging around earlier...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_detras">
		<text>Hey, Viktor’s right behind you. No—don’t look! He’ll see you!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_pico">
		<text>Is that guy carrying a damn pickaxe in his backpack? Hey... going artifact hunting or mining?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_sound_stalker_comida">
		<text>Look, that’s the one I told you about—the guy who found all that food... Lucky bastard.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_pda_tornillo">
		<text>Tornillo’s PDA... Let’s see what’s on it. Looks like he was doing some light research on the safest spots to find low-tier artifacts. It’s also full of photos from his time in the Zone — a few of them with his friend Cabo... Among the deleted files, there’s a note... It says: “It’s Kolyan. He’s the one who had me killed.” Who the hell is that? I need to figure out what to do with this PDA — it’s got valuable info. But Cabo deserves to see it too.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_nox">
		<text>I found a note in the stash... It reads: "If you’re reading this, then your dreams have guided you well. Your psychic sensitivity is above average — that’s why you were able to find this place before the others. Here, you’ll find what you need: the first Key, an artifact that will resonate with you and lead you to the other four. Together, the five will reveal a power that transcends all limits... but you’re not ready to understand it yet. As you move forward, the veil between your mind and what dwells above the Zone will grow thinner. Then I will be able to show you more. Follow the pulse. Do not stop, Nox." but there was no artifact there. I need to dig deeper — someone got here before me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_pda_centinela">
		<text>This PDA belongs to someone named "Sentinel". There are a few entries from a couple of days ago: "My leg wound is getting infected... I need a loan to pay for these damn antibiotics." Damn, poor guy. There’s another entry a few days later: “There’s this guy, Atreo. Came out of nowhere, says he can give me the money I need if I go with him to the swamps. Of course I said yes — even if I’m limping and it hurts, it beats losing my damn leg.” Guess it didn’t end well. That explains why the corpse was limping.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_hook_1">
		<text>An old sheet of paper, covered in notes passed between different people. The last entries read: "Couldn’t get in. There were too many of them, coming from every direction — looks like they’re marching south in massive numbers, fresh brains all nicely washed. My rifle broke from overuse, so I’m leaving it in the stash to fix it later. Dante, I’m gonna need that blue tape of yours — the ‘fix anything’ kind. Leaving you some supplies in return." The reply is written below in neat handwriting: "Came back wrecked from the Forest. I’m taking the supplies you left, and I’ll grab your Vintar to repair it at the workbench in the cemetery. Tank asked me to leave some backup weapons, so I’ll stash them in box #13, above the tunnel leading to Darkscape. Leaving some pills here too — you’ll need them. Until next time. —Dante" So we’ve got Dante... and another stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_hook_2">
		<text>Another worn-out piece of paper — looks like it’s passed through a lot of hands. The last note reads: "Hook, Tank, Vera — I saw a rookie trying to loot this stash. Looks like the seasonal shift exposed it. I’m moving everything to stash #7 and abandoning this one. Leaving one of the keys. Stay safe." Below it, written in cursive: "Goddamn it, Dante... always playing mysterious, moving stashes around, like we’ve got time to keep searching and searching. I left a really important mag here and now it’s gone. Lost my map with all the stash locations too. I don’t know which damn one is #7 — was it the boxcar on the bridge, the one over the Pripyat River... or the one in Darkscape!? Damn it, man... I swear I’m gonna knock your teeth in when I find you." The last note isn’t signed. But now we’ve got more names: Dante, Hook, Vera, and Tank.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_hook_3">
		<text>A crumpled ball of paper. Once unfolded, there’s a note inside: "Saw some people who used to be Clear Sky in Cordon. Are they planning something? Couldn’t stick around, but I’m leaving this warning so it doesn’t catch you off guard. Tank, thanks a lot for the artifact — makes carrying all this weight a lot easier. Left a few goodies in return. Stay safe, see you at the Bar." Below it, in different handwriting: "Guys, Monolith forces reached Cordon and sealed off the north. Looks like Duty is trying to hold them back, but there were a LOT of them. I don’t think they’ll last, so I’m heading through the swamps. I’ll try to leave intel at the pumping station, up top — you know where. Be careful... I heard they killed the trader Mark recently." Yeah... things are getting bad.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_hook_4">
		<text>A note scribbled on a napkin: "Guys, I came to the swamps to check on the Clear Sky situation. Looks like they’re making a comeback… They’re few, but well-armed, and I’ve seen them moving north at night. During the day, they keep a low profile — probably to avoid trouble with the military. I’ll have to go through Darkscape. Hope my mag is still in the rocks behind the gas station… or we’re gonna have a problem :) P.S. Took all the supplies. Left Dante’s key so he doesn’t start whining." Looks like this guy’s still pissed about his magazines... I need to check the next stash.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_leto">
		<text>Neat, almost calligraphic handwriting reads: "I came through again! But this time I got ahead of him! Managed to steal his stuff before he even noticed — what a complete idiot. It’s unbelievable they still fall for it every time I switch gas masks… stalkers are getting sloppier by the day." Below the note, there’s a messy, angry face scribbled: >:( The handwriting doesn’t match the calm script above...Was that someone else?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_pda_mago">
		<text>The Mage’s PDA... It’s locked. The only thing visible is a list of recent messages from the following contacts: Leto, Teeth, Kolyan, Sultan, Key, Borov, Bartender... Looks like he had some powerful connections. I should take this to Wolf.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_nota_mago">
		<text>A note on clean paper — unusually well-kept for the Zone: "Listen, Mage. I had to send a few of these idiots to camp near your position. I told them to wait for you, and they’ve got orders to join your cause when you’re ready to carry out the plan. There should be nine bandits — if fewer made it, ask them what the hell happened. I don’t want any of them hiding out in Cordon, or we’ll draw attention." — Pirate</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_foto_viper">
		<text>In the photo, there are two people wearing light blue and white camouflage suits... I’ve never seen gear like that in the Zone. They’re posing together, making hand signs at the camera. They look like good friends... The one on the right feels familiar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_arma_dogo">
		<text>I should take this to Dogo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_traje_viper">
		<text>Viper’s gonna be happy with what I found.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_cosas_pollo">
		<text>Pollo’s gonna pay me well for all the running around I had to do...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_pda_monolito_cruz">
		<text>The One Who Knows All repeated it a hundred thousand times: wait at these coordinates until the heretic shows himself. It’s been six days now, carrying out the will of the Monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_item_pda_zombie_boss">
		<text>We tracked a stalker who ran past us wounded. Saw him stop in the tunnel to catch his breath. We’re moving in... The guys are losing it. the stalker in the yellow jacket made some kind of hand signs and everything went to hell... I had to shoot them — they were attacking me. My head’s about to explode... I’m seeing double, colors all wrong… everything turns red sometimes, then blue... If anyone finds this PDA, please get it to Cold.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolito_cruz">
		<text>The Monolith was right… you’ve come.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_pantanos_camino_1">
		<text>Listen... I haven’t set foot in the Great Swamps in years. Got a lot of history with that place — none of it good. We go in careful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_pantanos_camino_1">
		<text>Got it. So... history, huh? What happened there?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_pantanos_camino_2">
		<text>Long story, friend. Real long. I’ll tell you another time, when we’re not on edge like this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_pantanos_camino_2">
		<text>Fine. You owe me that story.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_pantanos_camino_3">
		<text>I’ll cover you. Cross the fence and follow the tracks. I’ll stay behind, make sure no one’s on our tail.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_pantanos_vias_1">
		<text>Where do those tracks lead?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_vias_1">
		<text>Head east, they’ll take you back to Cordon. Past a tunnel, they lead into Darkscape... no man’s land.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_pantanos_vias_2">
		<text>And to the west?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_vias_2">
		<text>About a kilometer out, there are railway ruins torn apart by anomalies. Then there’s a bridge crossing the Pripyat River.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_pantanos_vias_3">
		<text>A bridge, huh… interesting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_vias_3">
		<text>I know you’re eager to explore the Zone, Viktor. But don’t get lost thinking ahead. Let’s stay focused. I don’t want to spend a second longer here than we have to.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_advertencia_1">
		<text>One important thing: don’t go through the water. The radiation will poison you bad.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_advertencia_2">
		<text>Viktor, better stay out of the grass. You’ll make noise, and that’s the kind of attention we don’t want.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_cem_1">
		<text>Hold up a second, friend. Since we’re here, let me make a quick stop.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_pantanos_cem_1">
		<text>Sure. What is it?/text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_cem_2">
		<text>Rest in peace, friends...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_pantanos_cem_3">
		<text>Alright, let’s move.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_llegando_1">
		<text>We’re almost there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_llegando_1">
		<text>Too quiet... I don’t like it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_llegando_2">
		<text>What the hell is that!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_llegando_2">
		<text>Shoot! It’s not human anymore!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_zombis_muertos_1">
		<text>I’ll stand watch. Take your time checking things out...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_zombis_muertos_1">
		<text>Alright, give me a minute.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viktor_vamonos_1">
		<text>No clues on the bodies. Sidorovich’s frequencies are missing, and there’s no sign of Atreo... I don’t get what happened.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mar_viper_vamonos_1">
		<text>We’ll have to ask around in Cordon if anyone’s seen Atreo. Let’s head back through the smuggler tunnel. We’ll use the cover of night so the military doesn’t gun us down. Let me know when you’re ready.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_asesinato_militar_0">
		<text>(Whispering) Shhh… this one’s mine. Turn off your flashlight and keep quiet.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viktor_asesinato_militar_1">
		<text>Didn’t know you had a silenced weapon...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_asesinato_militar_2">
		<text>They’re necessary. I’d recommend getting one... (sigh) Let’s get moving.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_asesinato_militar_3">
		<text>No! Turn it off-</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_viper_ya_en_base_0">
		<text>Well, Viktor — good run. No major trouble. Nicely done. I’m gonna go see a friend now. You’ll probably want to check in with Sidorovich. Good luck — come find me if you need anything.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_viktor_perros_1">
		<text>(Whistles, calling the dogs) Good… that worked.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_vovan_perros_1a">
		<text>Oh no! Here they come! Don’t let them get close!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_vovan_perros_1b">
		<text>Damn filthy dogs!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_vovan_perros_2">
		<text>Ah, for fuck’s sake... I thought you’d be more useful. Ended up doing most of the work myself.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_viktor_perros_3">
		<text>Idiot...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_1">
		<text>Monolith... I see them...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_2">
		<text>I see heretics dressed in red and black...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_3">
		<text>Infidels ahead!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_4">
		<text>Dstroy them in the name of the Monolith!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_5">
		<text>Follow the Monolith’s will!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_6">
		<text>Leave no one alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_7">
		<text>The Monolith commands us to fire before they can react.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_8">
		<text>FOR THE MONOLITH!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_deber_8b">
		<text>For the monolith!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_kir_1">
		<text>They’re flanking us from the hill!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_kir_2">
		<text>Take cover!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_kir_3">
		<text>Young man, come speak with me before you leave. We have unfinished business.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_kir_4a">
		<text>B.S.C. to Garbage, B.S.C. to Garbage — do you copy?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_msg_monolitos_kir_4b">
		<text>B.S.C. to Garbage, B.S.C. to Garbage — come in?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_leto_truco_msg_0">
		<text>Oh, yeah. I don’t have the artifact on me — follow me for a minute.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_leto_truco_msg_2">
		<text>(Laughs)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_leto_truco_msg_1">
		<text>Wow. Surprised you’re still conscious. But you’re not getting out of this. Nobody survives this...</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_leto_truco_viktor_msg_1">
		<text>What’s happening!? What is this!?</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_leto_truco_viktor_msg_2"> <!--sin voz-->
		<text>¡ATREUS!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_teleport_actor_viper">
		<text>Hey, friend! Welcome back. Do you remember what happened? Talk to me.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_zombie_boss_viktor_msg_1">
		<text>What the fuck!? HEY! Who are you!? I’ll shoot!</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_zombie_boss_viktor_msg_2">
		<text>So Leto went ahead and dealt with those stalkers on the way... Poor bastards. I should go see Viper — he’ll know how to track him down.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_reclutando_cabo_msg">
		<text>Alright. Got my gear. Let’s move!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_reclutando_dogo_msg">
		<text>Pay attention, stalker. You’re about to see an expert at work.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_reclutando_pollo_msg">
		<text>(Humming) When we find Atreo, I’m gonna gouge his fucking eyes out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_viper_msg_1">
		<text>Rookie, heads up. Grab your stuff — we’re moving.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_cabo_msg_2">
		<text>All set, sir! Ready!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_viper_msg_3">
		<text>Dogo! You can bring Linda out now — don’t forget the ammo crate.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_dogo_msg_4">
		<text>Yeah... time to take Linda out for a walk.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_viper_msg_5">
		<text>Rooster! You’re forgetting the medkits again...</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_pollo_msg_6">
		<text>Huh, could’ve sworn they were in my backpack. (laughs)</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_viper_msg_7">
		<text>Viktor! I can see the excitement in your eyes. Relax. We’ll find him.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_pre_viaje_viktor_msg_8">
		<text>(Embarrassed) I’m fine, don’t worry. (laughs)</text> 
	</string>
	
	<string id="esc_susto_pollo_msg_1">
		<text>(Mocking a Monolith soldier) “For the Monolith... attack the one in Duty colors....”</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_susto_cabo_msg_2">
		<text>POLLO! FOR FUCK’S SAKE! I thought you were a Monolith soldier!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_susto_pollo_msg_3">
		<text>(Laughter)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_susto_dogo_msg_4">
		<text>Can’t believe you fall for that every time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_susto_viktor_msg_5">
		<text>You should relax a little, Rookie..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_susto_viper_msg_6">
		<text>Enough! Stay sharp. Monolith could show up any second. Especially you, Rookie — you scare easy as it is.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_susto_pollo_msg_7">
		<text>Buzzkill...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_traje_cabo_dolg_msg">
		<text>(Whispering) Stalker... I heard you needed a suit. Come closer, let’s talk.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_bandidos_wolf_msg">
		<text>Noise on the roof! GO CHECK IT OUT!</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_wolf_ladron_msg">
		<text>Kid, we found the thief. Come by when you can — we need to talk about that bastard.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_wolf_ladron_msg_2">
		<text>Please, take care of my boys, kid.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_wolf_ladron_msg_3">
		<text>Kid, I’ve been going through the Mage’s PDA and found some things. Looks like he made a deal with some bandits to attack the rookie village... I’m counting on you — come see me when you can and I’ll explain everything.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_wolf_ladron_msg_3b">
		<text>Good work. Let’s find the next group.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_wolf_ladron_msg_3c">
		<text>Let’s move on to the next group.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="esc_wolf_ladron_msg_3d">
		<text>That should be all of them... The village is safe now. Come here — I’ve got something for you.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_arma_kir_msg_1">
		<text>Rookie Fedya, routine equipment check tonight. Don’t forget to bring your weapon.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_arma_cabo_msg_2">
		<text>Yes, Captain! I’ll have my gear ready for tonight.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_arma_viktor_msg_3">
		<text>You’re in deep shit, Cabo...</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_arma_cabo_msg_4">
		<text>Viktor, look... (whispering) Please — find my weapon. I’ll pay you well.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_tornillo_conpda_msg">
		<text>No… these photos aren’t even a month old. And now I’ll never see him again...</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_tornillo_sinpda_msg">
		<text>No, seriously. It’s strange Tornillo would slip up over something as basic as radiation. Something feels off... Am I missing something here? ...No. Leave it.</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="esc_tunel_boar_viktor_msg">
		<text>You fucking pig… tough bastard.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_general_msg_1">
		<text>Novato, hay pelusa quemada en ese túnel. Pasemos agachados y no hagas movimientos bruscos.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_general_msg_2">
		<text>Era broma stalker. No iba a correr hasta la base...</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_general_msg_3">
		<text>Sabes, este túnel antes tenía anomalías eléctricas. Un día vino un científico, puso unos aparatitos, apareció un artefacto y las anomalías desaparecieron para siempre.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_general_msg_4">
		<text>Escucha, novato. Gracias por la ayuda, creo que serás un gran stalker alguna vez Esos fantasmas sí que me dejaron mal de la cabeza. Ven y hablemos sobre la paga que te ganaste antes de que me duerma.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_msg_1">
		<text>¿No sientes algo raro? Escucho como... un zumbido.</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_msg_2">
		<text>¡SON ELLOS! ¡Son los fantasmas que me atacaron!</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_msg_3">
		<text>¡AGH! ¡Mi cabeza! ¡Siento las voces de los fantasmas!</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_fantasma_msg_4">
		<text>¡STALKER! ¡AHÍ ADELANTE! Hacia el NORTE, vi algo ¡Te lo juro!</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_msg_fantasma_1">
		<text>Stalker, no te alejes mucho de mí. Lo digo para que no te vaya a pasar nada...</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>
	<string id="esc_dogo_msg_fantasma_2">
		<text>¡Stalker, mueve el culo!</text> <!--sin voz-->
	</string>

	<string id="dar_viper_msg_1">
		<text>Pollo ¡No te quedes atrás! Te veo muy relajado.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_1">
		<text>Si si si. Ya voy, Capitán Viper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_2">
		<text>Eviten ir por la calle. Tomemos el camino a la derecha y usemos la cobertura de los árboles.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_3">
		<text>¿Los vieron, no? Hay varios. Avancen con la cabeza a gachas...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_1">
		<text>Jaja ¿Qué agache la cabeza? A la mierda con eso ¡Acá estoy monolitos, vengan con papi!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_1">
		<text>Tenemos un francotirador a la 1 en punto ¡Más adelante!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_4">
		<text>Lo veo, a cubierto ¡Viktor! Acercate. Te toca a tí.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_5">
		<text>¡FUEGO DE COBERTURA! ¡Corre Viktor! Al árbol de la izquierda. Quédate ahí hasta que recargue.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_primero">
		<text>¡Bien! Esperá ahí a que recargue...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_segundo">
		<text>¡Genial! Espera ahí, ve tu izquierda luego.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_tercero">
		<text>¡Vas bien, Viktor! Corré al árbol de tu derecha después.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_tercero_dogo">
		<text>Cuidado chico. No te cruces con el fuego de Linda si no quieres quedar sin piernas.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_cuarto">
		<text>¡Bien, amigo! Espera ahí. Luego zig-zaguea hasta el árbol a tu izquierda.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_quinto">
		<text>UF, Casi ¡Bien!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_francotirador_sexto">
		<text>Viktor! ¡Está a vista! Desde ahí puedes matarlo ¡Queda en tus manos!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_6">
		<text>Increíble... Espero que no haya más de estos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_2">
		<text>...Nos vendría bien un francotirador ahora mismo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_2">
		<text>(Risa)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_2">
		<text>Odio a los francotiradores. Son unos malditos maricas.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_6b">
		<text>Suficiente. Sigamos por los bordes de la calle que lleva al Este.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_3">
		<text>Cuidado. Hay una puta anomalía de fuego en medio de la calle.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_4">
		<text>¡JAJAJA! Miren como cayó ese monolito ¡Quedó todo tieso! ¡JAJA!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_7">
		<text>Atentos. Nos movemos al helicóptero más adelante. Tomemos un descanso ahí. De paso necesito vendarme, que estoy perdiendo sangre...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_5">
		<text>Te hecho una mano, tengo vendas de los científicos... Aunque la verdad son vendas normales con parches de los científicos. Pero igual sirven.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_8">
		<text>Uf... Paremos un rato. Cabo, haz guardia mientras, enseguida te acompaño. El resto, relájense un rato.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_3">
		<text>Tenían ventaja de terreno alto y aún así no pudieron con nosotros... Somos muy buenos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_3">
		<text>Que no se te suban los humos, novato. El mérito es mío.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_4">
		<text>Oh, ya veo. Muchas gracias, Dogo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_trodnik_msg_1">
		<text>¡Viper! Tenemos a tu chico, lo atrapamos hace rato ¿Dijiste que tenía chaqueta amarilla, verdad? te mando nuestras coordenadas.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_9">
		<text>¡Enseguida vamos! No le quiten los ojos de encima ni un segundo, es peligroso. Recuerda lo que hablamos. Viktor, ven. Hablemos y seguimos camino. Prepárense.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_trodnik_msg_2">
		<text>Tomate tu tiempo que lo tenemos a punta de cañón y no está armado, no irá a ninguna parte.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_5">
		<text>¿Esta es la gente que buscabamos? Pero si estaban vivos hace unos minutos...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_6">
		<text>No se ven bien. No hace falta ser científico para darse cuenta...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_10">
		<text>Mierda... Les advertí que no lo subestimen. Cabo, Dogo, cubran la puerta. Pollo, te toca cubrir el patio. ¡Viktor! Conmigo, busquemos cualquier pista de Atreo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_6">
		<text>¡Si, Capitán!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_trodnik_msg_3">
		<text>Una PDA con una nota de voz. La voy a reproducir: "Leto usó algún tipo de truco y se soltó. Noqueó a los chicos con un solo movimiento de su mano ¡Ni siquiera nos tocó! Al final, tenías razón con tu teoría. Solo estoy consciente por el casco que llevo... Tomen bloqueadores antes de acercarse.\n Saquennos de esta miseria."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_11">
		<text>Bueno, esto confirma la corazonada que te había mencionado, Viktor. El artefacto que lleva Leto le permite manipular campos de energía PSI, por eso nos hemos cruzado con estos zombis en más de una ocasión. Además tengo otra sospecha...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viktor_msg_1">
		<text>De ahí los zombis que vi antes en los pantanos ¿Y ahora qué hacemos? ¿cómo le seguimos el rastro siquiera?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_7">
		<text>¡Silencio! La puta radio está haciendo ruidos raros. Escuchen...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_radio_monolith">
		<text>Recibimos la señal del infiel (Interferencia) está en dirección al Valle Oscuro (Interferencia) está usando el artefacto para evadirnos, cambio.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_12">
		<text>Eso confirma mi otra sospecha. De alguna manera los monolitos están rastreando a Leto a través del artefacto. Es peligroso, pero hay que seguirlo hasta el Valle Oscuro... ¡Sigamos!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_8">
		<text>Algo anda mal, hay demasiado silencio.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_4">
		<text>Los mutantes deben haber escuchado todos los disparos de antes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_13">
		<text>¡Alto! Hay monolitos sobre el puente. Avancen con la cabeza a gachas. Dogo, va para ti eso también, no hagas un escándalo de nuevo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_5">
		<text>Está bien. No hay nada de qué preocuparse, me porto bien...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_14">
		<text>Ya nos falta poco. Hay un viejo túnel que podemos cruzar para llegar directo al Valle Oscuro. Si tenemos suerte, no tendrá anomalías en medio. Con eso deberíamos acortar distancias con Atreo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viktor_msg_2">
		<text>Tomemos cualquier atajo necesario. No podemos perderlo de nuevo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_9">
		<text>Si dejamos que nos gane más distancia, se va a llenar de putos monolitos cuando lleguemos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_7">
		<text>¿¡QUÉ ES ESO!? ¡QUÉ CARAJOS!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_6">
		<text>Es un pseudo gigante, novato. Prepárense todos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_10">
		<text>¿Por qué levanta la puta pierna? ¿Qué hace? ... ¡AAAAAAH!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_15">
		<text>No se descuiden. Revisen que no hayan perdido nada y sigamos hacia el desagüe que está adelante.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_7">
		<text>Ya estoy grande para esto.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_11">
		<text>¿Qué edad tenías, Dogo?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_dogo_msg_8">
		<text>49 años de pura testosterona.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_12">
		<text>(Risas por lo bajo)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_8">
		<text>¿Y ustedes? ¿Qué edad tienen?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_16">
		<text>37 años.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_pollo_msg_13">
		<text>32 añitos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_9">
		<text>Vaya ¿Y usted, Viktor?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viktor_msg_3">
		<text>22 años...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_cabo_msg_10">
		<text>Increíble. Soy el más joven del grupo...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dar_viper_msg_17">
		<text>Mucho cuidado con sus pasos. Revisen bien donde pisan que no voy por este camino hace años...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="val_llegada_viktor_0">
		<text>¿Y ahora para dónde vamos?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_viper_1">
		<text>Nos movemos a la granja al Sur-Oeste del Valle. Tengan cuidado, sospecho que vamos a ver más monolitos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_cabo_2">
		<text>Espero que me alcancen los perdigones. Ya me quedan pocos...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_pollo_3">
		<text>Yo traigo de reserva. No te preocupes, Cabo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_viper_0">
		<text>Revisen el lugar. Asegurense de que sea seguro.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_cabo_1">
		<text>Aquí hubo pelea hace poco...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_pollo_2">
		<text>Estos bandidos estan frescos. Cuidado.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_ituca_3">
		<text>¡Por favor, no disparen! ¡Hablaré!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_viktor_4">
		<text>Te conviene empezar a hablar. Y no intentes nada raro que estoy sin paciencia hoy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_dogo_5">
		<text>¡Metele un calcetin en la boca!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_llegada_base_viktor_5">
		<text>Pffft (Risas)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_sid_msg_0">
		<text>Me enteré que llegaron con vida al Valle Oscuro, y que necesitan hablar con Sultán. Resulta que tenemos algunos intereses en común, y he arreglado para que te reciba si lo ayudas con un pequeño asunto. Dile que vas de mi parte, Viktor ¡Y a ver cuándo te pasas por el bunker de nuevo! Tengo material nuevo...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_bandido_on_viktor_0">
		<text>Ahora parezco un bandido</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_bandido_off_viktor_0">
		<text>Ya no parezco un bandido</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_kolyan_viktor_0">
		<text>¿¡...Qué mierda!?</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trc_truck_matasanos_0"> 
		<text>¿Quién es? Si eres un mutante ¡Vete!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_viktor_1">
		<text>No soy un mutante...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_viktor_2">
		<text>Salí de una vez. Vine a rescatarte.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_matasanos_3">
		<text>¡No hay nadie!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_matasanos_4">
		<text>¡Limpia a los mutantes primero! ¡Luego saldré!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_viktor_5">
		<text>¿Mutantes? Mierda.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_viktor_6">
		<text>¡YA ESTÁ, BAJATE!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_matasanos_7">
		<text>Uf, menos mal. Enseguida bajo. Dame un segundo que junte mis cosas.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_viktor_8">
		<text>Quedate cerca mío, que está lleno de mierda este lugar.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_truck_matasanos_9">
		<text>Bien, voy pegado a ti. Por favor no salgas corriendo, no creo poder seguirte el paso.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_0">
		<text>¡Cuidado! ¡POR LA DERECHA!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_1">
		<text>¡Mierda! Estan llegando más. Voy a morir hoy ¡VOY A MORIR HOY!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_2">
		<text>No quiero morir :c</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_3">
		<text>¡Oh no! ¡Vienen más!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_4">
		<text>¡Bien! Dales su merecido ¡Cuidado, vienen más!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_5">
		<text>Mierda, Mierda ¡Mierda! No debí venir nunca a este lugar maldito.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_6">
		<text>¡No te mueras! ¡Yo no puedo con ellos!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_susto_matasanos_7">
		<text>¡Cuidado! ¡POR LA DERECHA!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_hit_matasanos_0">
		<text>¡Stalker, por aquí! ¡Me están por comer vivo, necesito ayuda!</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="val_back_matasanos_0">
		<text>Stalker, te debo una. Pásate a verme si necesitas que te suture o si quieres beber algo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_back_viktor_1">
		<text>Más vale que invites vos...</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="val_kashalot_recruit_dialog_0">
		<text>Putos novatos creídos. Se piensan que uno va a hacer lo que quieren. Te voy a acompañar, chico. De hecho, tu me vas a acompañar a mi. Guía el camino y yo guío a mi gente.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_viktor_recruit_dialog_1">
		<text>Como sea, vamos de una vez.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_kashalot_recruit_dialog_2">
		<text>Chicos, nos reunimos en la entrada del cementerio de camiones. Tomaremos lo que nos corresponde.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trc_inc_kashalot_0">
		<text>Bien ¿Estamos todos? Te hablo a ti, Chatarra. Siempre llegando tarde.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_bandido_1">
		<text>Si, estoy aquí. Llegué temprano esta vez.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_kashalot_2">
		<text>Tenemos refuerzos de parte de Kolyan, así que no me hagan pasar vergüenza, manga de inútiles. Vamos a limpiar el área y a recuperar el puesto de avanzada donde mataron a los nuestros.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_bandido_3">
		<text>(Entusiasmados)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_kashalot_4">
		<text>Yo invito las rondas después. Solo a los que sobrevivan. Jejeje, pero primero hay que ir al punto a capturar.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_kashalot_0">
		<text>¡Los veo! ¡Tomen posición y apoyen firmes los jodidos pies!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_viktor_1">
		<text>¡Ojo que son varios!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_kashalot_2">
		<text>Fácil ¿Alguna baja? Meh, no importa. Sigamos los que estamos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_bandido_3">
		<text>¿Hay premio para los que llevemos más bajas?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_kashalot_4">
		<text>Obvio. Pero voy a ser yo, o quizás este que nos mandó Kolyan. Lo veo bueno.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_viktor_5">
		<text>¿Cuál sería el premio?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_kashalot_6">
		<text>Naturalmente, MI PUTA SCAR. Pasado mañana me llega una escopeta que quiero hace bastante.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_1_bandido_7">
		<text>(Sapucay)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_2_kashalot_0">
		<text>Suelten las botellas, ya casi llegamos ¡Esta vez son más!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_2_kashalot_1">
		<text>Uf. Necesito un jodido trago. Acuerdense que yo invito luego ¡No mueran!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_2_kashalot_2">
		<text>Queda un solo punto ¡Siganme los buenos!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_3_kashalot_0">
		<text>¡Ahora vamos por nuestros colegas! A ver si encontramos su botín luego de limpiar estos putos cultistas ¡JA!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_3_kashalot_1">
		<text>¡Vienen más a las 9 en punto! ¡Aguanten, maricas!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_3_kashalot_2">
		<text>Bueno, vamos a sentarnos un rato. El puesto es nuestro de todas maneras. ¿Tu nombre era Viktor, verdad? Ven, charlemos un poco.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_3_viktor_3">
		<text>Bien, ya voy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_3_kashalot_4">
		<text>Te veo con hambre de revisar esos cuerpos. Adelante. luego charlamos.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_inc_smart_3_viktor_5">
		<text>(Risas por lo bajo)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trc_kashalot_hurt_1">
		<text>(Herido)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_kashalot_hurt_2">
		<text>(Herido) Otra cicatriz más...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_kashalot_hurt_3">
		<text>(Herido) Pongo la otra mejilla. Denme otro disparo los que se atrevan...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_kashalot_hurt_4">
		<text>(Herido) ¡Mierda!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_kashalot_hurt_5">
		<text>(Herido) Maldita sea. Mi brazo...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trc_kashalot_bandits_dead_0">
		<text>Inútiles. Solo quedamos tu y yo, Viktor. Siempre he dicho que si quieres que algo salga bien, debes hacerlo tu mismo.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="val_viktor_leto_0">
		<text>Ahora si, hijo de puta. Te tengo donde quería...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_viktor_leto_1">
		<text>Monolitos muertos... ¿Serán los que seguían a Atreo?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="val_viktor_leto_2">
		<text>Mas cuerpos... Debe estar cerca.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="labx18_entrada_leto_0">
		<text>Así que me encontraste... Te recomiendo que vuelvas por donde viniste.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_entrada_viktor_1">
		<text>No me voy a ningún lado.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_entrada_leto_2">
		<text>(Risas)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_entrada_viktor_3">
		<text>¿¡EH, qué pasa!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_entrada_leto_4">
		<text>Estoy muy ocupado ahora. No me molestes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_2_viktor_0">
		<text>¡Basta de trucos! ¡Da la cara, Cagón!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_2_atreo_1">
		<text>Me parece que no estás entendiendo lo que buscas. Este artefacto solo te va a traer problemas ¡Muchos problemas! Mejor dejamelo a mí...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_3_atreo_0">
		<text>¿Sabés por qué tuve que huir del cordón? ¡Me estaban siguiendo!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_3_viktor_1">
		<text>Más vale que te iban a seguir. Le robaste a todo el mundo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_3_atreo_2">
		<text>(Risas) No tenés idea de lo que está pasando.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_3_viktor_3">
		<text>No importa. Te voy a encontrar...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_espejo_viktor_0">
		<text>¡Deja de esconderte, cagón!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_fake_espejo_atreo_1">
		<text>Que curioso. Esconderme es imposible a esta altura. Y no lo digo por vos...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_puerta_primera_atreo_0">
		<text>Que terco que sos. No parece que vayas a frenar en ningún momento.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_puerta_primera_viktor_1">
		<text>¡Basta de trucos! ¡Dejá de intentar entrar en mi cabeza! ¡DAME EL ARTEFACTO!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_puerta_primera_atreo_2">
		<text>Empiezo a entender por qué fuiste elegido. Ademas de ser un cabeza dura, tu resistencia a emisiones psi es muy alta... Ya no puedo sostener la puerta.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_segundo_nivel_viktor_0">
		<text>¿¡Dónde estás!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_segundo_nivel_atreo_1">
		<text>No voy a salir tan fácil. Me vas a tener que buscar y cuando me encuentres va a ser muy tarde.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_segundo_nivel_viktor_2">
		<text>No sé para qué estás haciendo tiempo. Voy a encontrarte igual y ese artefacto va a ser mío.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_segundo_nivel_atreo_3">
		<text>¿Estás seguro? Yo pensaba lo mismo, y otros también. No sos diferente a nosotros.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_segundo_nivel_viktor_4">
		<text>¿¡DIFERENTE A QUIÉNES!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_segundo_nivel_atreo_5">
		<text>(Risas)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_0">
		<text>No pensé que fueses a llegar tan lejos. FALTANDO TAN POCO.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_viktor_1">
		<text>¿¡Tan poco para qué!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_2">
		<text>¡YA CASI! ¡TRES MINUTOS MÁS!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_viktor_3">
		<text>¿¡Tres minutos para qué!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_4">
		<text>(Risa maníaca)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_5">
		<text>(Risas) ¿Qué pasa? ¿No te podés mover?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_6">
		<text>Sova... Desgraciada hija de puta. Debí matarte cuando pude.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_viktor_7">
		<text>¿Sova? ¿Con quién habla?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_8">
		<text>Ozero ¡Espero que esa anomalía te haya hecho arder hasta las cenizas!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_viktor_9">
		<text>No sé quién esa gente. Está loco... Habla solo.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_10">
		<text>¡CALLATE, NO ME DEJÁS CONCENTRAR!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_11">
		<text>¡Nox! Me arruinaste la vida, hijo de puta. Espero que no puedas caminar entre los vivos nunca más.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_viktor_12">
		<text>¿¡Nox!? ¿Qué sabes de Nox?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_13">
		<text>¡Se van a arrepentir! ¡Todos se van a arrepentir!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_atreo_14">
		<text>No puede ser... Me rechazó ¿Y ahora qué hago?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="labx18_boss_viktor_15">
		<text>Ahora me vas a pagar. Eso vas a hacer...</text>
	</string>

	
</string_table>
