<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda">
		<text>Found PDA</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_buscador_artefactos">
		<text>Artifact Hunter’s PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_buscador_artefactos_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Files:%c[default] \n• Voice note - 8 days ago: "The bandits have me completely screwed... You get out of one debt just to fall into another, but today I saw an artifact blinking near the anomaly in the rookie village. Time to wipe out all my debts, Sparkplug. This is your moment. You can do it! No anomaly's gonna stop you! (Sounds of sparkplug falling into the anomaly)"
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_tornillo">
		<text>Tornillo’s PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_tornillo_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Files:%c[default] \n• Low-class Anomaly Research\n• Cheap Artifact Research\n• Article: Safe Ways to Hunt Artifacts\n• Article: Gravitational Anomalies\n• Various photos from life in the Zone, some pictures with Corporal Fedya. \n%c[guide_green] Deleted files:%c[default] \n• Text note: "It was Kolyan. He sent them to kill me."
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_centinela">
		<text>Sentinel’s PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_centinela_text">
		<text>
		%c[guide_blue] Files:%c[default] \n• Text note - 8 days ago: "The wound on my leg is getting infected. I need another loan to pay for the damn antibiotics."\n• Text note - 5 days ago: "There’s this guy, Atreus. Came out of nowhere saying he can get me the money I need if I go with him to the swamps. Of course I said yes. Even if I limp and it hurts like hell, it’s better than losing my fucking leg."
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_mago">
		<text>Andrés "Mage" PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_mago_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] PDA Locked:%c[default] \n%c[guide_green] Latest received messages:%c[default] \n• Leto — 11 unread messages.\n• Teeth — 2 unread messages.\n• Kolyan — 1 unread message.\n• Sultan — 2 unread messages.\n• Klyuch — 6 unread messages.\n• Borov — 1 unopened media file.\n• Bartender — 1 unread message.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_monolito_cruz">
		<text>Monolith of the Cross PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_monolito_cruz_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Files:%c[default] \n• Voice note - 2 days ago: The One Who Knows All repeated a hundred thousand times that I should wait at these coordinates until the heretic reveals himself. It has already been 6 days fulfilling the wishes of the Monolith.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_zombie_boss">
		<text>Zombified Stalker PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_zombie_boss_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Files:%c[default] \n• Voice note - 2 hours ago: We tracked a wounded Stalker who ran past us. Saw him stop in the tunnel to catch his breath. We're moving in." \n• Voice note - 1 hour ago: The guys are going insane... the Stalker in the yellow jacket made some gestures with his hands and everything went to hell... I had to shoot them, they were attacking me. \n• Voice note - 1 hour ago: My head is going to explode... I'm seeing double, and weird colors... Everything turns red sometimes, and blue other times... If anyone finds this PDA, please get it to Cold.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_trodnik">
		<text>Trodnik’s PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_pda_item_pda_trodnik_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Files:%c[default] \n• Voice note - 17 minutes ago: Leto used some kind of trick and broke free. He knocked the guys out with a single wave of his hand! He didn't even touch them! In the end, your theory was right. I'm only still conscious because of the helmet I'm wearing... Take blockers before getting close.\n Get us out of this misery.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
