<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas">
		<text>Notes Found</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_primera_nota_nox">
		<text>Nox’s First Note</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_primera_nota_nox_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• "If you're reading this, then your dreams guided you well.\n Your psychic sensitivity is stronger than most; that's why you were able to find this place before the others. \n Here, you will find what you seek: the first Key, an artifact that will resonate with you and lead you to the remaining four. Together, the five will unveil a power that transcends all limits... but you are not yet ready to understand it. \n As you move forward, the veil between your mind and what dwells above the Zone will grow thinner. Then I will be able to show you more.\n\n Follow the pulse. Do not stop." \n\n %c[guide_green]-Nox%c[default] \n\n The artifact mentioned in the hideout was missing. I need to find out more...
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_primera_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_primera_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• The latest notes read: "Couldn't get in. There were too many of them coming from every direction. Looks like they're marching South in insane numbers, with their brains freshly scrubbed clean. My Vintar broke down from overuse, so I'm leaving it in the stash to fix later. Dante, I'm gonna need that blue tape of yours — the 'all-purpose' one. Leaving you some supplies in exchange." \n• A reply to that note is written neatly underneath: "Came back wrecked from the Forest. I'm taking the supplies you left behind, and I'll bring your Vintar to repair it at the workbench in the cemetery. Tank asked me to leave some backup weapons there too. I'll stash them in Box #13, above the tunnel leading to Darkscape. Leaving some pills here too — I know you'll need them. See you around." \n\n %c[guide_green]-Dante%c[default]
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_segunda_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_segunda_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• The latest notes read: "Hook, Tank, Vera. Saw a rookie trying to loot this stash. Looks like the season change exposed it. I'm moving everything to Stash #7 and abandoning this one. Leaving one of the keys behind. Stay safe." \n\n %c[guide_green]-Dante%c[default] \n\n• Below that, written in cursive: "Fucking Dante, always acting mysterious, moving the stashes around like we have all the time in the world to keep searching and searching. I left a VERY important magazine here and now I can't find it. Lost my map with the stash names too. I don't know which damn one #7 is anymore. Was it the wagon on the bridge over the Pripyat River... or the wagon over Darkscape!? This pisses me off so much, man. I'm gonna punch you in the face next time I see you." The last note appears to be unsigned.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_tercera_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_tercera_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• "Saw some people who used to belong to Clear Sky in the Cordon. Wonder if they're planning something. Couldn't stay long, but I'm leaving this warning so you don't get caught off guard. Tank, thanks a lot for the artifact — helps me carry the weight better. Leaving a few goodies in return. Stay safe, see you at the Bar." \n• Below it, written in different handwriting: "Guys, the Monolith reached the Cordon and sealed off the North. Looks like Duty is trying to hold them back, but there were WAY too many. I don't think they'll last, so I'm heading through the swamps. I'll try to leave information at the pumping station, up top — you know the place. Be careful. Heard they killed the trader Mark not long ago."
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_cuarta_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_cuarta_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• "Guys, came to the swamps to check on the Clear Sky people. Looks like they're making a comeback... There aren't many of them, but they're well armed and moving North during the nights. During the day they stay hidden to avoid trouble with the military... I'll have to go through Darkscape. Hopefully my magazine is still in the rocks behind the gas station or we're gonna have a problem :) \n PS: Taking all the supplies. Leaving Dante's key behind so he doesn't cry about it later."
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_quinta_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #5</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_quinta_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• "Dante, Hook — ran into Tank and we're heading to the Hospital together. Hope to see you guys at the Bar! Miss you all. Signed: Vera." \n Another, much messier handwriting says: "YOU BETTER BRING MY MAGAZINES TO THE BAR, YOU HEAR ME!? VERA WANTS TO SEE YOU GUYS. I'LL LEAVE SUPPLIES ON TOP OF THE VALLEY BRIDGE, BUT KNOW THAT I'M DOING IT VERY ANGRILY. SIGNED: TAAAAANK-THE-ATHLETE, THE BEST STALKER IN THE ZONE!!!!!!!"
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_sexta_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #6</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_sexta_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Note:%c[default] \n• "Fixed the rifle, Hook. But I can't leave it here — the Valley's too active right now. You know how it is... I'm leaving it at the Truck Cemetery. Leaving the treasure hunter to help you find it, since our old stash there got destroyed by mutants. Bring gloves. The box is hot... You know how it works." \n\n %c[guide_green]-Dante%c[default]
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_septima_nota_hook">
		<text>Veterans’ Note #7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_notas_septima_nota_hook_text">
		<text>
			%c[guide_blue] Nota:%c[default] \n• "Asked the Doctor about the artifacts. Leto has the PSI manipulation one. Sounds like he doesn't really know how to use it, and Monolith is tracking him. A guy named Kolyan has the regeneration artifact. Don't know him personally, but apparently he's a pretty influential bandit. That would leave us with only two more to find, not counting ours. See you at the Hospital — let's hope your lead is good, Hook..." \n\n %c[guide_green]-Dante%c[default]
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>
